

ABOUT ME

Successful merchandising Professional with 8 years of experience in Smartphone industry. Extensive knowledge of sales strategies, colortheory, and consumerbehavior. Proven ability to drive sales and increase revenues.

Enthusiastic sales consultant with detailed knowledge of the fashion and cosmetic industries and a passionate drive to achieve sales targets.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth 29-05-1992

Father

Sageer yousuf

Nationality INDIAN

Marital status Married

LANGUAGES

- Malayalam
- English
- Hindi

SAHAL MS

MARKETING EXPERT



+919645224316

Sahalsageer786@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

OPPO ELECTRONICS KERALA PVT.LTD

ERNAKULAM,KERALA.INDIA Mar 2016- July 2019

Tech Hub

Mobile Retail Chain
Outlet, Service Center
Cochin, Kerala, India
Jan 2020 – Aug 2023

TVS Finance

Cochin, Kerala

Sep 2023 – Present

EDUCATION

GRADUATION IN BSC COMPUTER SCIENCE

HIGHER SECONDARY

SSLC

SALES EXECUTIVE

- The person in charge of 45-50 Outlets
- Handled more than 14 promoters and monitored theirsales
- Performance in sales from each shop wise
- Over counter combination of our different models
- Product display in the with reference to OPPO style
- As an exceptional leader with expertise in Smart phoneindustry and operations, achieved target and earned incentives by implementing innovative strategies.

STORE MANAGER

- Leadership of the team to complete the tasks and to meet goals
- Managing administrative duties including managing payrolls, budgets etc.
- Selection of team members and implementing training programs
- Managing employees of the organizations
- Analyzing new market areas to start new Stores.

FIELD OFFICER

- Managing day to day activities
- Add new customers
- Verifying their details and uploading it to the site.
- Adding shops to the field network

MAHATMA GANDHI UNIVERSITY 2013

GVHSS, KAITHARAM 2009

ST. ALOYSIUS HS, N.PARAVUR 2007

SKILLS

- Excellent communicator
- Customer Service
- Business Development
- Sales
- Training and mentoring
- Smart phone servicing

REFERENCE

1.TVS CREDIT

Mr. AMAL RAZIK A A Team manager TVSCREDIT Amal.razikaa@tvscredit.com 8592949728

2.TECH HUB

Mr. SHIJAS C K Managing Director Tech Hub Digital 8606579736

31-01-2024 North Paravur